<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LearnPopote</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_page">HomePageActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="access_your_classes_on_phone"> <b><i>Learn, Popote Ulipo!  </i></b></string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="title">LEARN</string>
    <string name="tag">…popote ulipo…</string>
    <string name="mobile_learning">Mobile Learning</string>
    <string name="copy">An app by Kenneth Mwenda</string>
    <string name="name">Your Official Names</string>
    <string name="nameHint">Please enter at least two names.</string>
    <string name="email">Email Address</string>
    <string name="emailHint">someone@example.com</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="phoneHint">+254 *** *** ****</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="passHint">Your Password</string>
    <string name="repeatPassword">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="pass2Hint">Password Again</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="signUp">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="forgotPass">Forgot Password</string>
    <string name="slideAlt">Slide main image</string>
    <string name="pagerIndicator">Pager indicator</string>
    <string name="goToLogin">Go to login</string>
    <string name="fbButtonAlt">Login with Facebook</string>
    <string name="googleButtonAlt">Login with Google</string>
    <string name="appLogoAlt">Application logo</string>
    <string name="bgImageAlt">Background image</string>
    <string name="step1">Step 1</string>
    <string name="step2">Step 2</string>
    <string name="step3">Step 3</string>
    <string name="selectCourse">Select from our wide range <br />of courses.</string>
    <string name="accessCourse">Access courses on any device, <br />any time.</string>
    <string name="completeCourse">Completion certificates issued <br />to all successful students!</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="apiKey">AIzaSyAz7727GL5v1bLFUR-ZxyelWZ19TVx4SDg</string>

    <string-array name="menuItems">
        <item>My Profile</item>
        <item>My Classes</item>
        <item>My Grades</item>
        <item>Suggested Courses</item>
        <item>Logout</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="userMap">userMap</string>

    <string name="introToHtml">
        HTML stands for HyperText Markup Language. It is used to design web pages using a markup language. HTML is the combination of Hypertext and Markup language. Hypertext defines the link between the web pages. A markup language is used to define the text document within tag which defines the structure of web pages. This language is used to annotate (make notes for the computer) text so that a machine can understand it and manipulate text accordingly. Most markup languages (e.g. HTML) are human-readable. The language uses tags to define what manipulation has to be done on the text.
\n
HTML is a markup language used by the browser to manipulate text, images, and other content, in order to display it in the required format. HTML was created by Tim Berners-Lee in 1991. The first-ever version of HTML was HTML 1.0, but the first standard version was HTML 2.0, published in 1999.
\n
Elements and Tags: HTML uses predefined tags and elements which tell the browser how to properly display the content. Remember to include closing tags. If omitted, the browser applies the effect of the opening tag until the end of the page.
\n
HTML page structure: The basic structure of an HTML page is laid out below. It contains the essential building-block elements (i.e. doctype declaration, HTML, head, title, and body elements) upon which all web pages are created.
\n
&lt;DOCTYPE! html&gt;: This is the document type declaration (not technically a tag). It declares a document as being an HTML document. The doctype declaration is not case-sensitive.\n
&lt;html&gt;: This is called the HTML root element. All other elements are contained within it.\n
&lt;head&gt;: The head tag contains the “behind the scenes” elements for a webpage. Elements within the head aren’t visible on the front-end of a webpage. HTML elements used inside the &lt;head&gt; element include:
\n
    &lt;style&gt;\n
    &lt;title&gt;\n
    &lt;base&gt;\n
    &lt;noscript&gt;\n
    &lt;script&gt;\n
    &lt;meta&gt;\n
    &lt;link&gt;
\n
&lt;body&gt;: the body tag is used to enclose all the visible content of a webpage. In other words, the body content is what the browser will show on the front-end.
\n
An HTML document can be created using any text editor. Save the text file using .html or .htm. Once saved as an HTML document, the file can be opened as a webpage in the browser.
\n
NOTE: Basic/built-in text editors are Notepad (Windows) and TextEdit (Macs). Basic text editors are entirely sufficient for when you’re just getting started. As you progress, there are many feature-rich text editors available which allow for greater function and flexibility.
\n
Features of HTML:
\n
    It is easy to learn and easy to use. \n
    It is platform-independent.\n
    Images, videos, and audio can be added to a web page.\n
    Hypertext can be added to text.\n
    It is a markup language.
\n
Why learn HTML?
\n
    It is a simple markup language. Its implementation is easy.\n
    It is used to create a website.\n
    Helps in developing fundamentals about web programming.\n
    Boost professional career.
\n
Advantages:
\n
    HTML is used to build websites.\n
    It is supported by all browsers.\n
    It can be integrated with other languages like CSS, JavaScript, etc.
\n
Disadvantages:
\n
    HTML can only create static webpages. For dynamic webpages, other languages have to be used.\n
    A large amount of code has to be written to create a simple web page.\n
    The security feature is not good.\n
    </string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>